<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Quickonf</title><link>https://tiramiseb.github.io/quickonf/</link><description>Recent content on Quickonf</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://tiramiseb.github.io/quickonf/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>https://tiramiseb.github.io/quickonf/frontpage.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tiramiseb.github.io/quickonf/frontpage.html</guid><description>With Quickonf, you are able to configure your Linux computers, and keep the configuration you want, using a simgle configuration file.
You may execute it whenever you want, to check your system is configured as needed or to fix some configuration you should not have changed.
After reinstalling your system or anytime you want, you simply have to run Quickonf and voilà, your system is (re)configured exactly how you had it before (as long as your configuration is described in your Quickonf configuration file, of course)!</description></item><item><title>Commands</title><link>https://tiramiseb.github.io/quickonf/commands.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tiramiseb.github.io/quickonf/commands.html</guid><description>Commands The following commands are available in the latest version of Quickonf. Use the field below to filter them.
alternatives.set apt.install apt.key apt.remove apt.source apt.upgrade debconf.set dpkg.install dpkg.version file.absent file.content file.directory file.extract file.move file.move.nocheck file.perm file.read file.symlink flatpak.install git.clone git.config git.hash github.latest github.latest.stable gnome.extension.install http.get.file http.get.var http.post.var json.get make nm.hotspot nm.import nm.wifi pip.install regexp.submatch snap.install snap.version stack.install systemd.enable tempdir user.dconf.set user.file.content user.file.directory user.git.clone user.git.config user.gnome.extension.enable user.go.env user.group user.systemd.enable user.vscode.extension.install user.xdg.userdir xdg.</description></item><item><title>Configuration language</title><link>https://tiramiseb.github.io/quickonf/language.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tiramiseb.github.io/quickonf/language.html</guid><description>Groups A Quickonf configuration file is composed of multiple sections, called groups. The group name starts at the beginning of the line, instructions are indented.
group name instruction A instruction B ... instruction G instruction H depending on instruction G instruction I depending on instruction G Indentations length and type (spaces or tabs) is not strict, you may use whichever you want. Keep in mind that, when mixing indentations, tabs are considered to be equivalent to aligning to multiples of 8 spaces (ie.</description></item><item><title>Introduction</title><link>https://tiramiseb.github.io/quickonf/intro.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tiramiseb.github.io/quickonf/intro.html</guid><description>Introduction Quickonf is a semi-automatic configuration tool for Linux desktop computers, allowing you to reinstall your Linux system and quickly get your favorite environment back.
It is especially useful if you reinstall Ubuntu every now and then and do not want to use the same user environment over and over (because sometimes, when keeping older configuration files, some app may disfunction).
Think Ansible, but as a single binary command tailored for local desktop usage.</description></item><item><title>Recipes</title><link>https://tiramiseb.github.io/quickonf/recipes.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tiramiseb.github.io/quickonf/recipes.html</guid><description>Recipes The following recipes are embedded in the latest version of Quickonf. Use the field below to filter them.
apt sources.list no automatic apt updates apt sources.list Change the sources list file for APT from a file
Variables:
src: Path of the file to use as sources.list no automatic apt updates Disable periodic apt update, upgrade, autoclean
No variables</description></item><item><title>User interface</title><link>https://tiramiseb.github.io/quickonf/ui.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tiramiseb.github.io/quickonf/ui.html</guid><description>User interface The interactive user interface is composed of two panes.
The left pane lists all groups (according to your configuration file), while the right pane shows details on the selected group.
Filters and details By default, groups are filtered so that only groups in need of a change are displayed. You can toggle this filter with the &amp;ldquo;F&amp;rdquo; key or the &amp;ldquo;Filter checks&amp;rdquo; button in the title bar.
If you need more details about actions that would be executed, you can toggle them with the &amp;ldquo;D&amp;rdquo; key or the &amp;ldquo;More details&amp;rdquo; button in the title bar.</description></item></channel></rss>